stocktradingtogo.com 2018-12-25

# PRIVACY POLICY - StockTrader.com

This Privacy Policy controls and governs your use and access to any and all of Reink Media Group, LLC’s websites: investor.com, StockBrokers.com, ForexBrokers.com, StockTrader.com, and InvestingTeacher.com (collectively the “Website”). Depending on your residency or other legal factors, you may be subject to additional, or different, terms and conditions. Please see below for further information. Please note that, to the extent additional, or different, terms and conditions apply, the Privacy Policy is hereby expressly modified to incorporate the same. 

**WEBSITE VISITORS**

Like most website operators, Reink Media collects non-personally identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Reink Media’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how its visitors use the Website. From time to time, Reink Media may release non-personally identifying information in the aggregate, e.g. by publishing a report on trends in the usage of the Website. 

Reink Media also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. Reink Media does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below. 

**GATHERING OF PERSONALLY-IDENTIFYING INFORMATION**

Certain visitors to the Website choose to interact with the Website in ways that require Reink Media to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Reink Media gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who use our forums to provide a username and email address. In each case, Reink Media collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with the Website. Visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Website-related activities. 

**AGGREGATED STATISTICS**

Reink Media may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to the Website. For instance, Reink Media may reveal how many views a particular streaming video broadcast had.

**PROTECTION OF CERTAIN PERSONALLY-IDENTIFYING INFORMATION**

Reink Media discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors, and affiliated organizations that (a) need to know that information in order to process it on Reink Media’s behalf or to provide services available on the Website, and (b) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors, and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using the Website, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. 

Reink Media will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than its employees, contractors, and affiliated organizations, as described above, Reink Media discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when Reink Media believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Reink Media, third-parties, or the public at large. 

If you are a registered user of the Website and have supplied your email address, Reink Media may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Reink Media, the Website and our products. We primarily use our blog to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. You have the right to opt out of receiving these type of email communications and need only notify us of your request to no longer receive such emails. With respect to other requests you may send to us (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Reink Media takes all measures reasonably calculated to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration, or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

**COOKIES**

A cookie or like-technology such as a web-beacon (“cookies”) is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. The Website uses cookies to help Reink Media identify and track visitors, their usage of the Website, and their website access preferences. All of Reink Media’s cookies are both Session (only during your current session) and Persistent (remains with you beyond current session). Users of Reink Media’s websites may also experience both Session and Persistent third-party cookies, as described in the reference chart below.

Visitors of the Website who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computer may opt out by either setting their internet browsers to refuse cookies before using the Website or, in the case of third-party cookies, by opting out directly with the third-party websites, by visiting the websites listed in the reference chart below and making the appropriate changes to the user preference setting. For clarity’s sake, most cookie-like technology such as web beacons are reliant on cookies to function properly, so in many instances declining cookies through a third-party website user preference setting will impair their functioning. Users should be advised that by opting out of receiving cookies, certain features of the Website may not function properly. Users should be further advised that by compliance with Reink Media’s informed consent policy, users have expressly granted their informed consent to the use of all cookies, including but not limited to, first-party Persistent cookies and third-party Session and Persistent cookies. For purposes of the informed consent policy, the duration of a user’s informed consent to the use of all cookies shall not exceed one-year. Following the expiration of the one-year period from the date of the user’s granting of informed consent, the user shall be again required to either grant Reink Media their informed consent for the use of cookies or opt out in a manner set forth above.

**INFORMED CONSENT WAIVER FOR COOKIES**

“By visiting this website and scrolling, you agree to our cookie policy and that we may use cookies for the best possible user experience.”

**INFORMATION REGARDING COOKIES AND ORIGIN SOURCE**

**Types of cookie** | **Who serves these cookies**  
---|---  
User experience cookies: These cookies are strictly for the use throughout our website and provide you with the best user experience. | StockBrokers.com, ForexBrokers.com, StockTrader.com, InvestingTeacher.com, FuturesBrokers.com, investor.com  
**Analytics cookies:** These cookies collect data that is used to help analyze how our websites are being used or how effective our marketing campaigns are. | Google, DoubleClick, CrazyEgg, AdWords, BingAds, MOZ, SEMRUsh, Google DFP, Double Verify, MaxMind, Quantcast, Direct Advertising Partnerships  
**Advertising cookies:** These cookies allow us to show relevant advertising messages to you based on your interests. | Facebook, Twitter, Adobe, Integral Ad Science, MOAT, White Ops, Adometry, Commission Junction, Fort Knox, Google DFP, Adwords, Bing Ads, Impact Radius, Flex Offers, Post Affiliate Pro, Finance Ads, Direct Advertising Partnerships  
  
**EUROPEAN UNION (EU) PRIVACY POLICY**

If you are an EU resident and/or an employee(s) or customer(s) of an EU resident, the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) mandates that you have certain privacy rights which may in part differ, as set forth below, from Reink Media’s standard Privacy Policy.

**HOW LONG WE WILL KEEP YOUR PERSONAL DATA**

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements; this retention period may extend past the point at which you close your account. Additionally, you may request that Reink Media delete your personal data as described below.

**YOUR CHOICE AND RIGHTS**

We welcome your inquiries and comments. You have the right to know what personal data we process about you and may request a copy. You are also entitled to have incorrect personal data about you corrected and you may in some cases ask us to delete your personal data. You can also object to certain personal data about you being processed and request that processing of your personal data be limited. Please note that the limitation or deletion of your personal data may prevent you from engaging in certain Website-related activities. You also have the right to receive your personal data in a machine-readable format and have the data transferred to another party responsible for data processing.

**PARENTAL CONSENT FOR CHILDREN’S PERSONAL DATA**

The GDPR requires parental consent for the processing of children’s personal data under the age of 16* (*age of consent may be lowered to 13 by applicable EU member state). You should advise Reink Media in the event you are under the age of 16, so that the appropriate parental consent may be obtained.

**HOW TO CONTACT US**

If you have any questions about how we process your personal data, or wish to exercise one of the aforementioned-rights, please feel free to contact us at admin@reinkmedia.com.

**CALIFORNIA PRIVACY POLICY**

If you are a California resident you have the right to request information from Reink Media regarding the manner in which Reink Media shares certain categories of your personal information with third parties, for the third parties’ marketing purposes. California law provides that you have the right to submit a request to Reink Media at its designated address and receive the following information:

– The categories of information Reink Media disclosed to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes during the preceding calendar year; and

– The names and addresses of the third parties that received such information, or if the nature of their business cannot be determined from the name, then examples of the products or services marketed.

You are entitled to receive a copy of this information in a standardized format and the information will not be specific to you individually. You may make such a request by contacting Reink Media by phone or mail/electronic mail at: Reink Media Group, LLC, 409 S. Washington, Royal Oak, Michigan 48067; (248) 591-4351; email: [admin@reinkmedia.com](mailto:admin@reinkmedia.com).

**PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES**

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Reink Media may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in its sole discretion. Reink Media encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Website after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
